rankflex.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Statement - RankFlex.com

_RankFlex.com_ does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from a contest or sweepstakes registration, the registration process for subscription sites or services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and forums), suggestions, voting/polling activities and transactional areas. Personally identifiable information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection. At such points of collection, the user will have the opportunity to indicate whether he or she would like to "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from _RankFlex.com_ and/or any third parties. Further, notwithstanding any opt out of promotional information by the user, _RankFlex.com_ reserves the right to contact a subscriber regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected.

_RankFlex.com_ reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. _RankFlex.com_ will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, users should be aware that _RankFlex.com_ may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through a _RankFlex.com_ site. _RankFlex.com_ is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information.

Additionally, users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the forums or in the chat areas of the _RankFlex.com_ sites, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in the user's communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of _RankFlex.com_.

Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of _RankFlex.com_ 's internet servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users should be aware that _RankFlex.com_ cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for _RankFlex.com_. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the _RankFlex.com_ Site.

Upon request, _RankFlex.com_ will allow any user to "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time. Additionally upon request, _RankFlex.com_ will use reasonable efforts to allow users to update/correct personal information previously submitted which the user states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Also, upon a user's request, _RankFlex.com_ will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from its database; however, it may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions.

We provide links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. We do not control these sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for any aspects of those sites, including their availability, content, accuracy, legality or delivery of services. You waive any claim resulting from your exposure to material on or through _RankFlex.com_ that is offensive, indecent, or otherwise objectionable.

The foregoing policies are effective as of October 12, 2009. _RankFlex.com_ reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

### Google Analytics

_RankFlex.com_ uses Google Analytics, a service from Google Inc.  
Please notice the [terms of service](http://www.google.com/intl/en_US/analytics/tos.html "Google TOS") for Google Analytics.
